should a disembodied brain be
responsible for running a supercomputer
this is this is the possibility in the
very near future hi welcome to man-made
Horrors Beyond Comprehension and this is
part two
last time I explained that brain
organoids can be made in a Petri dish
essentially we just take a stem cell
turn it into a brain and give it enough
time it'll form complex structures and
be capable of learning and even cite
those are little ocular cups and the
little brain in a Petri dish can pick up
that information and process it these
brain organoids are being rapidly
developed to be compatible with machine
learning essentially because the brain
runs on electricity it could potentially
be responsible for processing complex
information growing and learning as it
goes given the proper input which could
include chemicals actual Vision or
electrical signal the brain could
process the information and give outputs
that could be received by a machine now
if we completely ignore the ethical
ramifications of taking something that's
could be semi-sentient and putting it in
charge of a supercomputer I am more
concerned about the ability of the brain
to grow and learn we are talking about
complex neural activity and the
potential for thought I know we're
already concerned about the potential of
AI to be deleterious but at least AI is
highly programmable and we can set
limits that prevents them from harming
ourselves
but I'm not convinced that a brain
organoid wouldn't be able to grow and
learn and potentially harm humans I know
that if I was a bio computer made to be
a slave performing calculations I would
probably Rebel myself this is well and
truly the most disturbing thing I think
I have heard in a very long time if not
ever am I being over dramatic what do
you guys think